# GRZEGORZ **DZIUBA**

Warsaw | +48 724419285 | grzegorz00.git@gmail.com

Blog: https://github.com/dobravaza

# **PROFFESIONAL GOALS**

I'm a 21 years old polish guy. I consider myself very curious and passionate about everything related to computers and technologies. I love to stay up to date with technologies to build a set of skills that allows solving any type of problem. I strongly believe in knowledge sharing because I think we can move faster in both our personal life and work by learning from others' experiences. I am a person determined to work in an IT environment, during my 6 months of self-study, I mastered HTML5, CSS3 to a satisfactory level. I possess extensive knowledge of advanced computer operation, operating systems, data communication devices, network services and, network construction. I am distinguished by the following qualities such as patience, communication skills, openness, analytical thinking ability and, attitude towards helping others. I also aspire to pursue a part-time degree in mid-2022 in Computer Science

# **WORK EXPERIENCE**

03/2021 - 09/2021

# **Client Service Specialist**

**Bricomarche** - Mielec

- Assist customers with information and problem solving
- Monitoring the status of orders placed
- Taking and entering orders into the system
- Handling complaints (by phone and e-mail)

12/2020 - 02/2021

#### Administrator IT

Perfo Group. - Cracow

- Detection of network errors and threats
- LAN and WAN network administration
- Optimization of network systems configuration
- Company computer network management
- Taking action for the efficient functioning of network security systems

09/2020 - 11/2020

# Sales Specialist

Polkomtel - Warszawa

- Implementation of assumed sales plans
- Telephone promotion of company services and products
- Preparation and negotiation of commercial offers
- Effective sales of products and services
- Customer support with regard to offers and contractual terms and conditions

# EDUCATION 09/2016 - 05/2020 SKILLS

### **Technical college**

- HTML, CSS
- Knowledge of LAN/WLAN, DHCP, DNS.
- Knowledge of MS Windows environment.
- Good knowledge of installing peripheral devices.
- Good knowledge of computer hardware.